

Heeyang Jung

ROBOTICS · COMPUTER VISION · DEEP LEARNING

607, Seosuwon-ro, Gwonseon-gu, Suwon-si, Gyeonggi-do, 16392, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-3478-8484 | Muiyang1022@naver.com | Odlronmanb

"Opportunity did not knock until I built a door."

Summary

This is Heeyang Jung, who is enthusiastic about 3D Computer Vision & Robot Vision. Recently, I am interested in visual localization, SfM(Structure of Motion), and deep learning. I want to be an engineer who combines theory and practice. I want to be beneficial to people by exploring how the knowledge I learned can be used in the field or how it can be used.

Research Interests

Computer Vision Robot vision, Structure of Motion

Deep Learning generative model, unsupervised learning

SLAM Visual SLAM, VIO

Education

KwangWoon University Seoul, Korea

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2024(Expected)

- Current GPA: 4.34/4.50, Current Major GPA: 4.28/4.50
- Club: BARAM Robotics(Robotics Academic Group) [2022 Staff], Mar.2021-Present

Work Experience_

Ubiquitous Lab @ KwangWoon Univ

Seoul,Korea

Undergraduate Lab Intern(Advisor: Prof. Yonghoon Choi)

Jan. 2022 - Jun. 2022

Jun. 2022 - Present

- · Solving algorithm problems(BOJ, Programmers)
- Design deep Learning pipeline

Petnow Inc Seoul, Korea

Undergraduate R&D Division Intern(Advisor: CTO. Daehyun Pak)

- Improve biometric model named DNNet(Dog Nose Network)
- Improve backbone of DNNet
- Apply suitable loss function to DNNet

Skills

Programming Python, C/C++, Matlab **Framework** Pytorch, Tensorflow

DevOps Ros, Git **Languages** Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity _____

Neural Radiance Generative Adversarial Network for Photrealistic Space Design

Kwangwoon University

Mar .2023 - Jul. 2023

CAPSTONE

- Using [instant-NGP] [CycleGAN]
- Extended style transfer from 2D images to 3D objects
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository] (README.md will be made)

Door Lock System using deep metric learning

Baram robotics

PERSONAL TOY PROJECT

Sep. 2022 - Dec. 2022

• Improving original ResNet(Pytorch) / revising downsampling architecture [Github repository] (README.md will be made)

September 6, 2023 Heeyang Jung · Résumé

Reinforcement learning-based robot arm

Baram robotics PERSONAL TOY PROJECT Apr. 2022 - Jul. 2022

- Implementing the environment using gym(from openAl)
- · Connecting the agent program to the Robot arm in ROS
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository]

Game learning agent based reinforcement learning

Baram robotics

Sep. 2021 - Oct. 2021

PERSONAL TOY PROJECT

- Implementing the environment required for reinforcement learning
- Apply DQN algorithm to agent
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository]

First Runner Project

1ST STUDENT

- Studying Autonomous racing(F1tenth)
- Making AEB(automatic emergency braking) code
- Making wall following code

TresC3(Venture Inc), Korea Univ

Oct. 2021 - Feb. 2022

Educational Activities

AI Genius Academy Mentoring

TEACHING ASSISTANT

• Project Assistant with Arduino and Raspberry Pi

• Support students to experience AI and proceed with the project through a Teachable Machine

Organized by Micro School, TresC3

Nov. 2021

Samsung Electronics App Development Mentoring

TEACHING ASSISTANT

• MIT App Inventor training and Project Assistant

Organized by Micro School, TresC3

Jan. 2022